A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) FA489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2002.053: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2002; AC.2002.053; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2002.053.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - EO 9709 - SURDNA FOUNDATION - COMPREHENSIVE COMMUNITY REVITALIZATION PROGRAM: SOUTH BRONX, 1991-1998 (Box R3474, Box R3475)
    - EO 9709 - SURDNA FOUNDATION - COMPREHENSIVE COMMUNITY REVITALIZATION PROGRAM: SOUTH BRONX - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-1998 (Box R3474, Box R3475)
    - EO 9712 - REDEFINING PROGRESS - FISCAL POLICY PROGRAM, 1996-1999 (Box R3475)
    - EO 9713 - POVERTY AND RACE RESEARCH ACTION COUNCIL - POVERTY AND RACE JOURNAL, 1996-2001 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9717 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - SUCCESS FOR ALL AND ROOTS AND WINGS PROGRAMS, 1996-1998 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9718 - WATERFORD INSTITUTE, INC. - LITERACY SOFTWARE PROGRAM FOR PRESCHOOL STUDENTS, 1989-1997 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9727 - SUSTAINABLE AMERICA - NATIONAL NETWORK THAT PROMOTES ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1997-2000 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9731 - CENTRAL BROOKLYN PARTNERSHIP - ECONOJ'vllC SELF-SUFFICIENCY AND LITERACY, 1996-1997 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9732 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT LABORATORY PROJECT, 1997-2001 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9733 - NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT LAW PROJECT - WELFARE REFORM AND WORKFORCE POLICY PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3476)
    - EO 9742 - SAN FRANCISCO FOUNDATION COMMUNITY INITIATIVE FUNDS - COMMUNITY-BUILDING INITIATIVE, 1997-1999 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9744 - NEW SCHOOL FOR SOCIAL RESEARCH - CONFERENCE ON COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1998 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9746 - CONFERENCE BOARD, INC. - ASIA BUSINESS INITIATIVE, 1997-2000 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9802 - CENTER FOR COMMUNITY CHANGE - COALITION ON HUMAN NEEDS EMPLOYMENT SEMINARS PROJECT, 1997-1998 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9803 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - COMMUNITY-BUILDING CONFERENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9804 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY JOBS PROGRAM IN WASHINGTON STATE, 1998-2002 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9807 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - LOCAL GOVERNANCE STRUCTURE AND POLITICAL ENVIRONMENT IN METROPOLITAN AREAS, 1998-2002 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9808 - NATIONAL COMMITTEE FOR RESPONSIVE PHILANTHROPY - INFRASTRUCTURE DEVELOPMENT OF PROGRESSIVE POLICY AND ADVOCACY INSTITUTIONS, 1997-2002 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9809 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - TEMPORARY ASSISTANCE FOR NEEDY FAMILIES AND PUBLIC JOBS, 1996-1998 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9809 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - TEMPORARY ASSISTANCE FOR NEEDY FAMILIES AND PUBLIC JOBS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9815 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BASIC RIGHTS/COMMUNICATION STRATEGY ON RACIAL DISCOURSE, 1997-2001 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9817 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - CONFERENCE ON WELFARE REFORM, WORK, AND INCOME SECURITY, 1998 (Box R3477)
    - EO 9843 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - JOBS-PLUS, NEIGHBORHOOD JOBS INITIATIVE, AND CONNECTIONS TO WORK INITIATIVES, 1997-1999 (Box R3477)
- AC.2002.062: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2001; AC.2002.062; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2002.062.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GE 9217 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - STRENGTHEN CAPACITY TO PREPARE PROPOSALS, 1992-1998 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9421 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - RURAL ENERGY AND WATER SUPPLY UTILITIES IN INDIA, 1994-1998 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9505 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - LATIN AMERICAN FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ENERGY PLANNING, 1995-1998 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9604 - SOCIETY FOR CONSERVATION AND PROTECTION OF ENVIRONMENT (PAKISTAN) - ASSIST NGO AND COMMUNITY-BASED ORGANIZATIONS TO ACHIEVE FINANCIAL SUSTAINABILITY, 1995-1998 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9612 - E CO. - INITIATIVES IN PLANT OIL AND AQUACULTURE, AND WORKSHOP ON ENERGY ANALYSIS, 1996-1999 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9701 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - ELECTRIC VEHICLES FOR USE IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1996-1998 (Box R3478)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - EVCO: South Africa, 2002.062.001 (Item 2002.062.001)
      - EVCO: India, 2002.062.002 (Item 2002.062.002)
      - EVCO: Thailand, 2002.062.003 (Item 2002.062.003)
      - EVCO: Chile, 2002.062.004 (Item 2002.062.004)
      - EVCO: China, 2002.062.005 (Item 2002.062.005)
    - GE 9701 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - ELECTRIC VEHICLES FOR USE IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9705 - FOUNDATION FOR BUSINESS AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPEMENT (SWITZERLAND) - GREENBOOK FOR THE INTERNET, 1997-1999 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9706 - LEADERSHIP FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT INTERNATIONAL, INC. - LEAD EUROPE, 1996-1999 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9707 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - SOLAR CENTURY COMPONENT OF CLIMATE PROTECTION INITIATIVE, 1997-1999 (Box R3478)
    - GE 9811 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - CORE SUPPORT, 1997-1998 (Box R3478)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2002.062.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - HS 9026 - NIGERIAN INSTITUTE FOR SCHOOL AND ECONOMIC RESEARCH - TASK FORCE MEETING, 1990-1992 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9126 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - REDUCING TOBACCO USE IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1990-1994 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9242 - IMPERIAL COLLEGE OF SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY AND MEDICINE - CHILD DEVELOPMENT IN GHANA, 1992-1993 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9335 - UNIVERSITY OF COLOMBO (SRI LANKA) - CONFERENCE ON MALARIA PATHOGENESIS AND CLINICAL MANIFESTATIONS, 1993-1998 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9440 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - DIVISION OF FAMILY HEALTH - ADOLESCENT HEALTH, 1994-2001 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9503 - MBOI, NAFSIAH - BOOK ON WOMEN'S HEALTH IN INDONESIA, 1994-1998 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9512 - MEXICO - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - CHILDHOOD DIARRHEAL DISEASE, 1993-1997 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9512 - MEXICO - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - CHILDHOOD DIARRHEAL DISEASE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1997 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9606 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - SOCIAL SCIENCE AND MEDICAL ANTHROPOLOGI CAL RESEARCH IN SOUTHEAST AND SOUTH ASIA, 1996-1999 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9612 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC HEALTH (MEXICO) - REGIONAL MEETING FOR THE AMERICAS ON INTERNATIONAL HEALTH AGENCIES, 1996-1999 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9702 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - CONFERENCE ON "ECONOMICS OF TOBACCO CONTROL: TOWARD AND OPTIMAL MIX", 1997-1998 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9707 - BANGLADESH RURAL ADVANCEMENT COMMITTEE - WORKSHOP ON WOMEN'S HEALTH IN COMMUNITY, 1997-1998 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9710 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - HEALTH INSTITUTIONS MAPPING PROJECT, 1997-1999 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9712 - ZIMBABWE - HEALTH AND CHILD WELFARE (MINISTRY OF) - "AFRICAN INITIATIVE OF INDEPENDENT GROUP FOR GLOBAL HEALTH", 1997-1999 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9714 - KAROLINSKA INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - MEASUREMENT OF HEALTH INEQUITIES CONCEPTUAL WORKING GROUP, 1997 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9715 - TRANSNATIONAL FAMILY RESEARCH INSTITUTE, MOSCOW (RUSSIA) - "INEQUITY IN THE FACE OF DEATH IN RUSSIA", 1997-1999 (Box R3479)
    - HS 9720 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SEMINAR ON "VIOLENCE IN LATIN AMERICA", 1997-1998 (Box R3480)
    - HS 9727 - CHUNG, MICHAEL HOONBAE - SOCIOCULTURAL BARRIERS TO CATARACT SURGERY IN INDIA, 1997-1998 (Box R3480)
    - HS 9728 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY INITIATIVE, 1997-1999 (Box R3480)
    - HS 9802 - MEXICAN HEALTH FOUNDATION - HEALTH INEQUALITIES IN MEXICO, 1997-1999 (Box R3480)
    - HS 9805 - NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR THE CENTERS FOR DISEASE CONTROL AND PREVENTION, INC. - CONFERENCE ON EMERGING INFECTIOUS DISEASE, 1997-1998 (Box R3480)
    - HS 9806 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON COMMUNITY-BASED APPROACHES TO TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL, 1997-1998 (Box R3480)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2002.062.3; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - PS 9439 - INSTITUTO DE BIOLOGIA Y MEDECINA EXPERIMENTAL (ARGENTINA) - ENZYME B-N-ACETYGLUCOSAMINIDASE IN HUMAN FERTILIZATION, 1994-2000 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9515 - INTERNATIONAL PROJECTS ASSISTANCE SERVICES - POST-ABORTION SERVICES AND CLINICAL TRAINING IN PREVENTION AND TREATMENT OF ABORTION, 1995-1997 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9609 - ZAYAN, AHMED - NGO DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMS, 1996-1999 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9610 - SILLA, MUSA SAMBA - MONOGRAPH ON POPULATION POLICY AND DIALOGUE IN GAMBIA, KENYA AND ZIMBABWE, 1996-2000 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9611 - INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL ECONOMICS - FUTURE OF U.S. FOREIGN AID, 1996-2000 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9616 - FAMJLY CARE INTERNATIONAL - RESOURCE GUIDE FOR PREVENTION AND MANAGEMENT OF UNSAFE ABORTION, 1996-2000 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9701 - PEKING UNIVERSITY - RURAL FAMILY PLANNING SYSTEM, 1991-2000 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9705 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - MECLIZJNE AND NAUSEA ASSOCIATED WITH EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION, 1997-1999 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9708 - INSTITUTO DE BIOLOGIA Y MEDICINA EXPERIMENTAL - CONTRACEPTIVE USE OF EPIDIDYMAL PROTEIN, 1991-1999 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9506 - UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND - ESTABLISH POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT ADVISORY GROUP, 1995-1997 (Box R3480)
    - PS 9709 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - DISSEMINATE INFORMATION ON IMPLEMENTATION OF CAIRO PLAN OF ACTION AT CAIRO PLUS 5 MEETINGS, 1997-1999 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9710 - CAMPINAS CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND CONTROL OF MATERNAL AND INFANT MORTALITY (CEMICAMP) (BRAZIL) - SESSION ON ADOLESCENT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AT VI CONFERENCE ON MATERNAL AND NEONATAL HEALTH, 1997-1998 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9711 - YOUTH ALIVE CLUB (UGANDA) - HIV/AIDS PROGRAMS, 1996-2000 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9713 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF ALLERGY AND INFECTIOUS DISEASES - SEXUALLY-TRANSMITTED DISEASES AND ADOLESCENTS, 1992-2001 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9716 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - IMPLEMENTATION OF 1994 CAIRO PROGRAMME OF ACTION IN AFRICA, 1997-1998 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9717 - TIDES CENTER - DISTRIBUTE BOOK ON NEGOTIATING WOMEN'S RIGHTS, 1997-2001 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9721 - POPULATION COUNCIL - TESTIN IN SERTOLIGERM CELL INTERACTIONS, 1995-1998 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9725 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - CAIRO IMPLEMENTATION POLICY AND FINANCIAL ISSUES, 1997-1998 (Box R3481)
    - PS 9726 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION, WESTERN HEMISPHERE REGION - INTEGRATING HIV/STI PREVENTION IN FAMILY PLANNING, 1997-1999 (Box R3482)
    - PS 9803 - POPULATION COUNCIL - MEDICAL MENSTRUAL REGULATION PRODUCT, 1997-1999 (Box R3482)
  - BD, AC.2002.062.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - BD 9617 - AMERICAN DOCUMENTARY - HIGH IMPACT TELEVISION'S RACE INITIATIVE, 1996-1998 (Box R3482)
    - BD 9703 - AMERICAN LEADERSHIP FORUM - LEADERSHIP ROUND TABLE, 1995-1998 (Box R3482)
    - BD 9704 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR ECONOMIC ALTERNATIVES - COMMITTEE ON THE POLITICAL ECONOMY OF THE GOOD SOCIETY (RESCINDED), 1996-1998 (Box R3482)
    - BD 9706 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON CIVIL RIGHTS AND EDUCATIONAL POLICY, 1997-1998 (Box R3482)
    - BD 9807 - COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAMINATION BOARD - NATIONAL TASK FORCE ON MINORITY HIGH ACHIEVEMENT'S DISCUSSIONS, 1998-1999 (Box R3482)
  - Global Engagement (GEE), AC.2002.062.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GEE 9701 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - FUTURE OF U.S. FOREIGN ASSISTANCE, 1997-1998 (Box R3482)
    - GEE 9702 - INTERACTION: AMERICAN COUNCIL FOR VOLUNTARY INTERNATIONAL ACTION - U.S. GLOBAL ENGAGEMENT PROJECT, 1997-1999 (Box R3482)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2002.062.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9614 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - NON-PROLIFERATION OF WEAPONS IN THE MIDDLE EAST, 1996-1999 (Box R3482)
    - IS 9632 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - LESSONS OF TRACK II DIPLOMACY, 1996-1999 (Box R3482)
    - IS 9705 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - DISSEMINATE STUDY ON AMERICAN NUCLEAR DIPLOMACY WITH NORTH KOREA, 1997-1999 (Box R3482)
    - IS 9706 - CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY - ENERGY AND SECURITY: CONFIDENCE BUILDING MEASURES, 1997 (Box R3482)
    - IS 9707 - TWENTIETH CENTURY FUND, INC. - NUCLEAR POLICY REVIEW PROJECT, 1997-1998 (Box R3482)
    - IS 9714 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MANAGING THE ATOM PROJECT, 1997-1999 (Box R3482)
- AC.2002.063: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-2002; AC.2002.063; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - International Security (IS), AC.2002.063.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9719 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - ABOLITION OF WEAPONS ON INDIAN SUBCONTINENT, 1995-1998 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9722 - MIDDLE EAST INSTITUTE - U.S.-IRAN RELATIONS, 1997-1999 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9727 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY COOPERATION WITH INDIA, 1997-1999 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9728 - CHEMICAL AND BIOLOGICAL ARMS CONTROL INSTITUTE - JOINT INDO-U.S. EFFORT RE BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS, 1995-2001 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9729 - ARMS CONTROL ASSOCIATION - (ACA) - DISTRIBUTION OF "ARMS CONTROL TODAY", 1993-2001 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9803 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - CONSULTANGY ARRANGEMENT FOR ORPHEUS MULTIMEDIA, 1996-2002 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9807 - CHINA DEFENSE SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY INFORMATION CENTER - HANDBOOK ON ARMS CONTROL AND DISARMAMENT, 1995-2001 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9810 - STOCKHOLM INTERNATIONAL PEACE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - IRANIAN AND AMERICAN ACADEMICS MEETING, 1998-1999 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9820 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - INDIA - U.S. COOPERATION IN HIGH-TECHNOLOGY CONVENTIONAL WEAPONS, 1997-2001 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9823 - ASIA SOCIETY - SOUTH ASIA AFTER INDIA AND PAKISTAN'S NUCLEAR TESTS WORKSHOP, 1998-1999 (Box R3483)
    - IS 9824 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - KOREAN PENINSULA SECURITY RESEARCH, 1998 (Box R3483)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2002.063.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - SI 9518 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - NATIONAL DIALOGUE ON BALANCED BUDGET AMENDMENT, 1995-2000 (Box R3483)
    - SI 9524 - ASSOCIATION OF BLACK FOUNDATION EXECUTIVES - SECOND ROUND GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-1999 (Box R3483)
    - SI 9606 - GRAHAM, KENNEDY - "PLANETARY INTEREST" AMONG POLICYMAKERS WORLDWIDE, 1994-1998 (Box R3483)
    - SI 9616 - AMERICAN COMMUNICATIONS FOUNDATION - NETWORK ACCESS PROJECT, 1996-1998 (Box R3483)
    - SI 9619 - TIME DOLLAR INSTITUTE - "STRATEGIC PLAN" PROJECT, 1996-1997 (Box R3483)
    - SI 9716 - INSTITUTE FOR ALTERNATIVE JOURNALISM - MEDIA AND DEMOCRACY CONGRESS II, 1996-2001 (Box R3484)
    - SI 9706 - ETV ENDOWMENT OF SOUTH CAROLINA - TELEVISION SERIES "MISSION TO PLANET EARTH", 1996-2001 (Box R3484)
    - SI 9707 - CONSORTIUM FOR THE NATIONAL EQUAL JUSTICE LIBRARY - OPERATING COSTS, 1996-1998 (Box R3484)
    - SI 9713 - TELEVISION TRUST FOR THE ENVIRONMENT (ENGLAND) - PROJECT "HANDS ON: IT WORKS", 1996-1999 (Box R3484)
    - SI 9721 - VIDEAZIMUT (CANADA) - RIGHT TO COMMUNICATE AND COMMUNICATION OF RIGHTS SEMINAR, 1997-1998 (Box R3484)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2002.063.3; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AI 9602 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN {SOUTH AFRICA) - LECTURESHIP/RESEARCH EXCHANGE PROGRAM IN ANTHROPOLOGY, 1994-2002 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9611 - AFRICAN STUDIES ASSOCIATION - AFRICANA LIBRARIANSHIP IN THE 21ST CENTURY CONFERENCE, 1996-1998 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9612 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - SEMINAR ON ECONOMIC REFORM AND INVESTMENT IN EDUCATION IN FRANCOPHONE AFRICA, 1996-1998 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9616 - CENTER FOR GLOBAL EDUCATION AND DEVELOPMENT - INITIATIVES IN HIGHER EDUCATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1996-1999 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9702 - AMERICAN ASSEMBLY - EVALUATION OF "AFRICA AND U.S. NATIONAL INTERESTS" CONFERENCE, 1997-1998 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9705 - TAF COMPANY LTD. (KENYA) - WIZNET PROJECT FOR CHILDREN TO LEARN SKILLS IN ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATION, 1996-1999 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9709 - AFRICAN MEDICAL AND RESEARCH FOUNDATION (KENYA) - DOMESTIC WATER AND ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH IN EAST AFRICA, 1997-1998 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9711 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - "DAEDALUS" ISSUE ON SOUTH AFRICA, 1997-2001 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9713 - GLOBAL FUND FOR WOMEN - SURVEY ON NEEDS AND CONCERNS OF WOMEN IN DIFFERENT REGIONS OF AFRICA, 1997-1998 (Box R3484)
    - AI 9714 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - CONFERENCE ON "SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY FOR AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT: PARTNERSHIPS IN A GLOBAL ECONOMY", 1997-1999 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9716 - NEW SCHOOL FOR SOCIAL RESEARCH - SCHOOL-TO-SCHOOL PROGRAM TO ASSIST SCHOOLS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1997-1998 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9717 - FAMILY PLANNING PRIVATE SECTOR (KENYA) - 1998 CALENDAR ON FAMILY EQUITIY ISSUES, 1997-1998 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9719 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - WORKSHOP ON SEXUAL HARASSMENT AND ABUSE, 1996-1999 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9720 - HYDE, KARIN A. L. - EXPANSION OF EDUCATIONAL OPPORTUNITIES IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9723 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - CONFERENCE ON ROLE OF U.S. HIGHER EDUCATION IN GLOBAL HUMAN CAPACITY DEVELOPMENT, 1997 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9801 - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH CENTRE (IDRC) (CANADA) - AFRICAN TECHNOLOGY POLICY STUDIES NETWORK, 1993-1999 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9803 - NYERERE FOUNDATION (TANZANIA) - CONVERSATIONS ON PHILANTHROPY WITH U.S. FOUNDATIONS, 1997-1999 (Box R3485)
    - AI 9804 - KAISER FAMILY FOUNDATION - AFRICAN RENAISSANCE CONFERENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3485)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.063.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 90034 - CONTRACEPTIVE DEVELOPMENT - GOSSYPOL STUDIES, 1980-1993 (Box R3486)
    - RF 90034 #79 - NORTH CAROLINA STATE UNIVERSITY - GOSSYPOL, 1982-1998 (Box R3486)
    - RF 90075 - NITROGEN FIXATION IN NON-LEGUMES, 1990 (Box R3486)
    - RF 90090 - U.S. ENERGY PROGRAM - RF'S INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE PROJECT, 1990-1993 (Box R3486)
    - RF 90090 - U.S. ENERGY PROGRAM - RF'S INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1993 (Box R3486)
    - RF 91009 - PESTICIDE USE: ENVIRONMENT AND HEALTH, 1991-1996 (Box R3486)
    - RF 91009 #9 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - PESTICIDES AND RICE, FISH, FROGS AND MOLLUSKS, 1996-2000 (Box R3486)
- AC.2002.075: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2002; AC.2002.075; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.075.1; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - RF 91013 #492 - QUEENS COLLEGE, NEW YORK - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1988-1998 (Box R3487)
    - RF 91032 - BIOMEDICAL TRAINING AND RESEARCH, 1992-1996 (Box R3487)
    - RF 91077 - BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING JN LATIN AMERICA AND AFRICA, 1991-1994 (Box R3487)
    - RF 91077 #8 - UNIVERSITE NATIONALE DE COTE D'IVOIRE (IVORY COAST) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR SANGARE ABDOURAHAMANE, 1994-2001 (Box R3487)
    - RF 92015 - (ENERGY INITIATIVES) - SUPERIOR ENERGY TECHNOLOGIES FOR DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3487)
    - RF 92015 #11 - ENVIRONMENTAL ENTERPRISES ASSISTANCE FUND - ASSISTANCE TO SMALL CENTRAL AMERICAN COMPANIES IN PREPARATION OF ENERGY PROJECTS, 1996-1999 (Box R3487)
    - RF 92038 #453 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - AFRICAN AGRJCULTURE INSTITUTE, 1998-1999 (Box R3487, Box R3488)
    - RF 92038 #453 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - AFRICAN AGRJCULTURE INSTITUTE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-1999 (Box R3487, Box R3488)
    - RF 92038 #488 - ONYANGO, ADELHEID - ADIA: BREAST FEEDING AND GROWTH BEYOND TWELVE MONTHS, 1994-1999 (Box R3488)
    - RF 92038 #492 - MWANGI, SYMON - ADIA: MAIZE IMPROVEMENT IN KENYA, 1994-2002 (Box R3488)
    - RF 92038 #496 - HABIB, ADAM - ADIA: SOUTH AFRICA'S UNCERTAIN TRANSITION, 1994-2000 (Box R3488)
    - RF 92058 - FERTILIZER-EFFICIENT MAIZE FOR SOUTHERN AFRICA), 1992-1995 (Box R3489)
    - RF 92058 #4 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) ? EVALUATION OF NITROGEN-USE EFFICIENT AND OTHER MAIZE GENOTYPES IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1998 (Box R3489)
    - RF 92059 #172 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL DE LA PLATA (ARGENTINA) - DISMANTLING OF LIGHT-HARVESTING COMPLEXES DURING SENESCENCE, 1982-2001 (Box R3489)
    - RF 92074 - URBAN INSTITUTE - EMPLOYMENT DISCRIMINATION TEST IN LOS ANGELES, 1992-1999 (Box R3489)
    - RF 92084 - NATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGY BOARD OF CAMEROON - BOARD DEVELOPMENT, 1987-1998 (Box R3489)
    - RF 92087 #10 - POPULATION COUNCIL, INC. - NORPLANT IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1996-1998 (Box R3490)
    - RF 92092 #75 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH (PATH) - PUBLICATION AND DISSEMINATION OF NEWSLETTER GLOBAL ACCESS TO STD DIAGNOSTICS, 1992-1998 (Box R3490)
    - RF 92092 #78 - CHRISTIAN MEDICAL COLLEGE AND HOSPITAL (INDIA) - RISK FACTORS FOR ACQUIRING HIV INFECTION, 1994-1997 (Box R3490)
    - RF 92093 - (INTERNATIONAL ENERGY PROJECT DEVELOPMENT) - CO-GENERATION, END-USE EFFICIENCY AND BIOMASS-BASED ENERGY SYSTEMS, 1992-1998 (Box R3490)
    - RF 93001 - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF CEREALS, 1984-1996 (Box R3490, Box R3491)
    - 930013-531 - UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DO RIO DE JANEIRO (BRAZIL) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (RACE RELATIONS AND BLACK CULTURE RESEARCH PROGRAM) (NUCLEO DA COR), 1993-2001 (Box R3491)
    - 930013-534 - WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (NORTHWEST CENTER FOR COMPARATIVE AMERICAN CULTURES AND RACE RELATIONS), 1994-1998 (Box R3491)
    - 930013-542 - UNIVERSIDADE DE SAO PAULO (BRAZIL) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (NUCLEO DE ESTUDOS DA VIOLENCIA), 1994-1998 (Box R3491)
    - 930013-542 - UNIVERSIDADE DE SAO PAULO (BRAZIL) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (NUCLEO DE ESTUDOS DA VIOLENCIA) - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1998 (Box R3491)
    - RF 93019 #133 - COUNCIL FOR EDUCATIONAL ADVANCEMENT - INTERNATONAL EDUCATION CONSORTIUM - CHART NETWORK, 1995-1998 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #185 - INSTITUTE OF BASIC MEDICAL SCIENCES - CHINESE ACADEMY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - BIOTECHNOLOGY FELLOWSHIP FOR ZHANG MEILIN, 1990-1999 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #204 - SRI VENKATESWARA UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETICALLY ENGINEERED BACULOVIRUSES FOR PEST CONTROL, 1993-2000 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #214 - VERCESI, ANIBAL EUGENIO, 1990-1999 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #215 - UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DE MINAS GERAIS (BRAZIL) - TRANSFECTI ON OF TOXOPLASMA GONDII, 1993-1998 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #220 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL AUTONOMA DE MEXICO - DETECTION OF DE NOVO RECOMBINATION IN THE CYP21 GENE IN HUMAN SPERM DNA, 1993-1999 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93022 #221 - INSTITUTE FOR RESEARCH IN REPRODUCTION (INDIA) - ROLE OF 5A-REDUCTASE IN METABOLISM OF ANDROGENS, 1992-1998 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93029 #7 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN FERTILITY REGULATION, 1993-2000 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93029 #8 - PRINCE HENRY'S INSTITUTE OF MEDICAL RESEARCH (AUSTRALIA) - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN FERTILITY REGULATION, 1993-1998 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93031 #523 - MAINA, JOYCE GICHIKU - ADIA: AMINO ACIDS IN TILAPINE DIETS BASED ON SUNFLOWER AND GROUNDNUT MEALS, 1995-2002 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93031 #550 - KAMBEWA, PATRICK - ADIA: INSTITUTIONAL ANALYSIS OF THE LEGUME SEED SECTOR IN MALAWI, 1995-1997 (Box R3492)
    - RF 93035 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - STUDENT ASSESSMENT DEMONSTRATION PROJECT, 1991-1999 (Box R3493, Box R3494)
    - RF 93035 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - STUDENT ASSESSMENT DEMONSTRATION PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-1999 (Box R3493, Box R3494)
    - RF 93038 #33 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER - MAIZE DATABASE FOR KENYA, 1991-1998 (Box R3494)
    - RF 93039 #85 - DIAW, MARITEUW CHIMERE - SSRF: INLAND FISHERIES AND AQUACULTURE IN SOUTHERN CAMEROON, 1992-2001 (Box R3494)
    - RF 93039 #87 - GOCKOWSKI, JAMES JEROME - SSRF: TECHNOLOGICAL INNOVATION IN FOREST MARGINS, 1994-2001 (Box R3494)
- AC.2002.078: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2001; AC.2002.078; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes